cuckold-society.com 2018-08-28

# Privacy Policy

Cuckold Society, its partners and affiliates are deeply committed to protecting the privacy and concerns our Internet users may have. We have outlined below information and our guidelines that we observe for responsible management of our client and customer information. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: **[Cuckold Society](http://www.cuckold-society.com/)**. For the privacy policy pertaining to our dating site and members area, please refer to our dating partner's privacy policy located at: <http://adultfriendfinder.com/go/page/privacy.html>

#### Information Automatically Logged

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Additionally, we use your IP address to determine network traffic based per country of origin from aggreggated data. 

#### Information We Collect

Our site operates on behalf of advertisers who compensate us for sales and/or leads. We collect personal information only when you submit a form and consent to it. You may visit our website anonymously and are not required to submit any personal information. Information collected from these forms are logged and transmitted to our advertisers. Any information you transmit to our advertisers are protected under the individual advertiser's privacy policy which we require the advertiser to include and is located directly underneath any form you submit to them. 

#### What We Do With Your Information

Any of the information we collected from you may be used in any of the following means:   
Periodical emails or to notify you of updates of our site or advertiser websites.  
To subscribe you to advertiser websites.  
You may opt-out and permanently unsubscribe from either of these services by clicking the unsubscribe links that are included in all communications sent to your email. We will not contact you by any other means. 

#### Use of Cookies

Our website uses cookies to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information as you move from page to page on our website. We also aggregate data from cookies to offer a better site experience. 

#### Information Use to Third Parties

We only allow trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you to access your information, so long as those parties agree to treat this information as confidential. We may also release your information when appropriate, to comply with the law or to protect our rights and/or safety as necessary. Non-personal information (such as IP addresses) may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

#### External Links

This site contains links to other sites that we do not own or control. These third party sites have their own independent privacy policies, as such, we cannot be liable for their content or activities. 

#### Compliance with Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)

We do not allow anyone under the age of 18 years old to join our website. All products and services on our website are directed towards adults only. We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act). 

#### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control (IP, date and website addresses). 

#### Online Use Only

This privacy policy is applicable only to the information you submit to us through our website and not to information collected offline. 

#### Changes and Updates

Any updates or changes made to this privacy policy will be updated on this page. 

#### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us at:   
55 Northfield Drive East Suite 184  
Waterloo, Ontario  
N2K 3T6  

By using our website, you consent to the terms of our privacy policy.
